thelashop.com 2019-08-13

# Security & Privacy - TheLAShop.com

### Security

TheLAshop.com uses the most advanced 256-Bit encrypted software available. Our site is secured by 256bit SSL and is diligent about protecting your privacy and personal information. The data center we used is compliant to PCI Data Security Standards (PCI DSS).

### Privacy Policy

We care about your privacy. TheLAShop.com is committed to respect your privacy and to comply with applicable data protection and privacy laws. This privacy policy describes how we collect and use personal data.

We collect your personal data and other information when you make a purchase, use, register or subscribe into our products and services, take part in campaigns or research or otherwise interact with us. We do not sell, lease, rent or otherwise disclose your personal data to third parties. You have a right to know what personal data we hold about you. You have a right to unsubscribe from direct marketing messages or ‘unsubscribe’-link from email and to request that we stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes or on other compelling legal grounds. You may achieve your rights by contacting us or by managing your account and choices through available profile management tools on your device and our services. However, if you opt-out from marketing and other communications from TheLAShop.com, especially if you wish us to delete or stop processing your personal data, this may also mean that we may not be able to continue to provide the services to you.

We will occasionally update this Policy to reflect changes in our products and services, and to clarify our practices based on experience and customer feedback. And we recommend that you re-visit this Policy from time to time to learn of any such changes to this Policy.

* * *

Thank you for using our shopping system

TheLAShop.com

Headquarters:  
185 N Sunset Avenue  
City of Industry, CA 91744

Phone: 1-888-525-9222  
Fax: 1-626-336-2894

Homepage: www.thelashop.com  
Email: sales@thelashop.com
